I'm a nurse
#phrase
I'm a medical student
I'm an Ambulance officer
#phrase
I want to help you
Why did you call an ambulance?
#phrase
Tell me your medical history
Asthma
Epilepsy
Diabetes
Stroke
Heart attack history
#phrase
Do you take any regular medication?
Do you have pain?
#phrase
Where is the pain?
Can you describe the pain?
#phrase
Crushing
Tight
Sharp
Stabbing
Burning
What does it feel like?
#phrase
When did the pain start?
What makes the pain better?
#phrase
What makes the pain worse?
Have you taken anything for the pain?
#phrase
I want to know how bad your pain is
If 1 is good and 10 is bad
#phrase
Where are you on the scale?
Can you walk?
#phrase
When did you last have something to eat or drink?
Have you had any water?
#phrase
I'm going to put a needle in your arm so i can give you medication. Is that alright?
Do you have health insurance?
#phrase
Would you like to go to a public hospital or private hospital?