Classifier
Person
#classifier #nsw
Animal
Vehicle
#classifier #nsw
So
I want to show a car crash
Phrase demonstraion #phrase
Car
#classifier #nsw
Car crash
Woman
Phrase demonstrating specifing a detail about a classifier sign #classifier
Dog
Dog is shown on Asphyxia's right hand, patting the lap twice
#classifier
Person walking dog
Demonstration of classifier sign usage #classifier
Dog runs ahead
Motorbike, Motorcycle
Established sign for Motorbike #nsw
driving a vehicle
Classifier signing a vehicle driving forward #nsw #classifier
motorbike stops
Demonstration of a vehicle stopping using classifier signing #nsw #classifier
two people
Two people shown using classifier signing #nsw #classifier
two people meeting
Two people shown meeting, using classifier signing #nsw #classifier